

Mahtab Ul Alam Chowdhury

Address: Baridhara DOHS, Lane 05, House 324

Contact: 01715316305

Email: mahtabchowdhury43@gmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mahtab-ul-alam-

chowdhury-99b56724b

Career Objective

A dedicated and focused individual pursuing a Bachelor of Business Administration with a strong leadership, teamwork, and problem-solving background. I am committed to leveraging my skills and experience from academic projects and extracurricular activities to explore new opportunities and contribute effectively to organizational success. I seek a challenging role that offers professional growth and allows me to apply my computer proficiency and communication abilities to achieve personal and professional goals.

Academic Qualifications

North South University- Undergraduate - Present

- CGPA 0.00 on a scale of 4.00
- Department of Business Administration

Nizampur Government College, Chittagong- 2021

- CGPA 5.00 on a scale of 5.00
- Science

Mazharul Haque Chowdhury High School, Chittagong- 2019

- GPA 5.00 on a scale of 5.00
- Science

Work Experience

NY Trading Limited, Dhaka Stock Exchange Limited Intern

July 2023- Present

Job Responsibilities:

- Learning market trends and executing orders.
- Built strong client relationships to drive growth and retention.

English Olympiad Bangladesh

February 2022- Present

Job Responsibilities:

- Acting as the face of the English Olympiad in my institution.
- Assisted in organizing and coordinating seminars and EO Season 2 & 3, ensuring efficient resource allocation and volunteer engagement.
- Collaborate on joint campaigns, workshops, or promotional activities.

Executive-Online Communication & Social Media Management

July 2020 – September 2022

Job Responsibilities:

- Managed order tracking, processing, and fulfillment.
- Addressed customer inquiries and concerns
- Ensured timely processing and delivery
- Provided attentive customer support

Extracurricular Activities

Debate Club Member – Maruwf Model International School, Chittagong June 2014 – January 2019

- Remained a general member since 2014, rising to the position of second leader in 2016 and the position of debate club leader in 2017, serving as the chief debtor
- Planned and led club meetings, fostering an environment for improving debating skills through discussions, presentations, and debate competitions.
- Coordinated with teachers and club members to organize events and workshops, enhancing participants' abilities.

Scout Team Member - Mirsharai S.M. Model Primary School

January 2012 – December 2013

• Served as the 'Flag Bearer' in the team

Scout Team Member - Maruwf Model International School

January 2015- December 2018

• Active team member in the team

English Olympiad Bangladesh

February 2022 – Present

- Working as a 'Campus Ambassador'
- Served as the 'Organizing Committee Member & Invigilator' for the English Olympiad Season 3

Skills

- MS office
- Oral Communication
- Leadership skill
- Problem-solving abilities
- Teamwork

Language

- Bangla Native
- English Business Fluent (Listening, Speaking, Reading and writing)

Reference

Md. Abu Sayeed Chowdhury
 Chief Executive Officer
 NY Trading Limited, Dhaka Stock Exchange Limited
 Email: abu.sayeed@nytradingltd.com